孩子们 我永远不会忘记
Kids, I'll never forget the first time
我第一次跟你们妈妈表白
I told your mother I loved her.
那是在纽约的一个雨天
It was a rainy day in New York.
我们刚吃过一顿巨难吃的午饭
We just had a horrible lunch.
要看的电影又没座了
The movie we wanted to see was sold out,
我只是看着她
and I just looked at her
说出了 我爱你
and said, "I love you."
坦白心迹对我来说其实挺难
It was a big deal for me.
我很久没跟女孩表白了 自从
I hadn't said that to a girl since...
我爱你 罗宾
I love you, Robin.
我认真的
I'm serious.
你还记得当初我们怎么分开的么
Do you remember why we broke up in the first place?
我们问彼此 今后五年
We asked each other, "Where do you want
想去哪里呢”
to be in five years?"
我们的答案有着天壤之别
And our answers were just too different.
你看 五年过去了
Well, it's five years later,
现在我们在哪里呢
and where are we?
我们还站在这个
Standing on the roof
我初次吻你的屋顶
where I kissed youfor the first time.
我知道这挺不容易接受的
I know this is a lot to process,
我不是要给你什么压力
so no pressure here.
只是问问 你怎么想的呢
Just... what do you think?
啊 我说 你也累够呛啦 大半夜的
You know what? You're exhausted, it's late.
咱去挺尸吧哈
Let's just go to sleep.
晚安哈
Well, good night.
尼玛我干了些什么啊
What the hell was that?
没事 我可以弥补
Okay, I can fix this.
我偷偷去野营的时候
I-I was just temporarily insane because of my Lyme disease,
被虱子叮了 得了莱姆病
which I got on a camping trip that I didn't tell her about
所以 所以我刚才突然抽了
because... I go camping in secret.
绝了
Perfect.
或者我就说 对不起 咱还是好朋友
Or I could say, "I'm sorry, we're great as friends.
刚才那些就当我没说过”
Let's just forget I ever said anything."
唔 这个听着好点
Yeah, that's probably better.
准备 出动
Okay, here goes.
我偷偷去露营来着
I go camping in secret.
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十七集
翻译: 邵小庚 Mr Gao Roy 加菲猪 园丁姐姐
后期+统筹: Cathy 安达小充 校对: Andie 园丁姐姐
HIMYM字幕组倾情奉献！
喔 泰德 好吧
Wow, Ted, I... wow, okay.
你得让我慢慢说
You got to give me a minute here.
恩 慢慢说
Yeah, of course.
恩 唔 我觉得 我们得谈谈
Okay, um, we need to t-talk about this.
昨天的这个时候 我在佛蒙特
This time yesterday, I was in Vermont
刚刚跟人订婚
engaged to another man.
我是说 我的情绪还混乱着呢
I mean, it's been 24 hours of emotional mayhem,
这一天还没结束
and, and the day is still not over.
我向老天发誓
I mean, I swear to God,
要是今天谁还给我惊喜 我绝对狠狠抽他一顿
if there's any more surprises, I'm gonna hit someone!
亲爱的同志
... comrade.
这意思是
That means,
你好啊 工友
"Hello, coworker."
我们要回到俄罗斯母亲怀抱啦 准备好没
You ready for our trip to Mother Russia?
对了 国际新闻邀请罗宾阿姨去莫斯科
Oh, yeah, Aunt Robin was thrilled World Wide News
报道马勒斯尼沙狂欢节 她兴奋坏了
asked her to go to Moscow to cover Maslenitsa.
不过 当她发现这是个年度牛油节的时候
She was less thrilled to discover
她就没那么兴奋了
Maslenitsa is the city's annual butter festival.
更宓氖 她得在那呆整整一礼拜
Even worse, she'd spend an entire week with all those
跟那些油乎乎的俄国人还有她的致命敌 帕特里斯
buttery Russians and her archenemy Patrice.
咱们的飞机是晚上九点 不是早上
Uh, our flight leaves at 9:00 p.m., not a.m.
老天爷啊 帕特里斯
God... Patrice!
可是罗宾 日程上写的是早上九点
But, Robin, the schedule says 9:00 a.m.
机票上写的也是早上九点
and my ticket says 9:00 a.m.
所有的电邮提醒都是早上九点
and all the e-mail reminders said 9:00 a.m.
在楼下车里的我们老板也说是
and our boss in the car downstairs said...
闭嘴吧 我听见了
Okay, Patrice, I get it!
哦不
Oh, no!
裤子飞过去了 接住
Pair of pants coming in hot!
抗噪声耳机
Noise-canceling headphones.
那个我用不着
Oh, I don't need 'em.
你得在帕特里斯旁边坐十个小时哦 亲
It's a ten-hour flight and your sitting next to Patrice.
老天爷啊 我的止咳糖浆呢
Oh, God, where's my cough syrup?
没事没事 来得及
You're gonna make it.
我帮你把包拎下去
I'll bring your bag down.
我的鞋呢 老子的鞋呢
Where are my shoes? Where are my shoes?!
别担心 我没事
Don't worry. It's fine.
-咱俩那事 -快去吧
-And look, about all this... -Just go.
-再见 -回见
-Good-bye. -Bye.
我怎么没亲她啊
Why didn't I kiss her?
等我回来 我们继续
We'll continue this when I get back.
喂
Hello.
我知道挺早的
I know it's early,
但是 你能不能来酒吧跟我见一面啊 你自个
but can you meet me at the bar right now, alone?
我就来
I'm on my way.
我去酒吧见泰德一面
I got to meet Ted at the bar.
现在才早上七点啊
It's 7:00 a.m.
哥们 泰德总得有点界限吧
Man, Ted really needs to work on his boundaries.
嘘 你俩真心吵啊
Shh, guys, seriously.
你怎么在我俩床上啊
Why are you in our bed?
我坐着醉鬼列车 正好被困在这了
I took the drunk train and got stuck out here.
哎呀呀 宿醉好难受啊
Oh, God, I am so hungover.
哦 老天 莉莉没穿咪咪罩啊
Oh, God, Lily's not wearing a bra!
嘘
Shh!
宝贝 拜拜
Bye, baby.
你说如果
Do you think...?
我预感接下来的的话我一点也不想听
Okay, I already know I don't want to hear this.
你说如果我们爱爱了
Do you think that if we did it...
预感很对 一点不想听
Yeah, I was right. I don't want to hear this.
我非常非常的神勇
...and I did a really good job...
请滚蛋
Please leave.
那有没有可能 这货就会变成我的种呢
...that I could turn that into my baby?
我觉得我要吐了
I think I'm gonna throw up.
-晨吐吗  -显然不是
-Morning sickness?  -No.
很疯狂 对吧
It's crazy, right?
你震惊了没
Are you shocked?
不 我没有震惊 你就是爱罗宾
No, I'm not shocked. You're in love with Robin.
你还记得
Do you remember back
圣诞节的时候她情绪低落 你都不知道原因是啥
at Christmas when she was upset, you didn't even know why,
就花了8个小时准备圣诞的灯光
and you spent eight hours setting up Christmas lights
在公寓里等着 就为了让她高兴起来
in the apartment just to cheer her up.
这是精神基友应该做的 精神基友
That was a platonic friend thing. A platonic friend thing?
真的么 泰德 让我问你一个问题
Really? Ted,let me ask you a question.
你会为我那么做么
Would you have done that for me?
你也许会的 你就是这么好的一个朋友 泰德
You probably would have.You're such a good friend, Ted.
你也是 哥们
You, too, buddy.
我要去城里了
I'm going into the city.
就是 我走了以后
Just, while I'm gone,
不要乱翻我们的东西
don't go snooping around in our stuff.
我知道你认为我们有一盘春宫带藏在某个地方
I know you think we have a sex tape hidden somewhere,
所以我帮你免去一个麻烦 我们没有 拜拜
so I'll save you the trouble.We don't. Good-bye.
在巴尼的视线中这个瞬间是这样的
Here's that moment from Barney's perspective.
我们有一盘春宫带藏在某个地方
We have a sex tape hidden somewhere.
接受挑战
Challenge accepted.
又是罗宾
Robin again?
为什么每个人前仆后继的追罗宾
Why does everyone keep going after Robin?
为什么就没有一个人中意老娘呢
How come no one ever takes a run at me?
巴尼每天都在追你
Barney hits on you every day.
对 不过他就是想和我滚床单
Yeah, but he just wants to bang me.
我想要来真的
I want something real.
我知道 宝贝
I know, babe.
双A清洁公司
Double A Cleaning.
康斯薇拉 我是巴尼
Consuela, it's Barney.
我需要你和那些女孩们下午来帮忙
I need you and the girls for the afternoon.
当然 马上来 巴尼先生
Of course, right away, Mr. Barney.
你现在在家么
Are you at home now?
不 我在长岛的一栋房子里
No, I'm at a house on Long Island.
我会告诉你细节的
I'll text you the details.
工作量很大 这地方被洗劫了
It's a big job. The place has been ransacked.
我们会搞定的
We'll get right on it.
谢谢 康斯薇拉 你最好了
Thanks, Consuela, you're the best.
泰德 我知道对于你和罗宾之间这事
Ted, I know you're ready to go
你已经准备好要继续了
with this whole you-and-Robin thing,
但是她准备好了么
but is she ready to go?
她准备好了么 额
Is she ready to go? Um...
额 等我回来
Mmm, we'll continue this...
我们再继续
when I get back.
所以
So...
你确定不是这样
Are you sure that it wasn't...?
等我回来 我们再继续吧
We'll continue this when I get back.
好的
Okay.
神马 不
What?! No!
可恶 莉莉 你为什么总是跟我对着干
Damn it, Lily, why are you rooting against me?
我不是跟你对着干
I'm not rooting against you.
不 你就是
Yes, you are.
不 我没有
No, I'm not.
是 她就是的
Yes, she was.
你看 与此同时
You see, at that very moment...
长期赌局
"Long-term bets"?
莉莉赌 巴尼将会死于谋杀
Lily bets Marshall that Barney will die by murder
马修赌 罗宾将永远不会归还他们的吹风机
Marshall bets Lily that Robin will never return their hairdryer
莉莉赌 泰德以后会变成秃顶
lily bets marshall that ted'll go bald.
马修赌 要是泰德变成秃顶 一定会很帅气
marshall bets lily that if ted goes bald, he'll totally pull it off
额滴神呀 他们把我们的生活作为赌局
My God! They're placing bets on our lives.
不好意思 泰德秃顶是不可能帅的
And I'm sorry, Ted cannot pull off bald.
你们认识泰德  我是对的吧
You know Ted. I'm right about this.
泰德 我是你的好朋友 我为什么要跟你对着干呢
Ted, I'm your best friend. Why would I root against you?
莉莉赌 泰德和罗宾最后不会走到一起
Lily bets Marshall that Ted and Robin won't end up together.
这就是为什么
That's why.
所以 莉莉打赌我和罗宾不能走到一起
So, Lily was betting against me and Robin.
我还不知道
I just didn't know it.
好吧 你想和罗宾一起么
Okay, you want to make it work with Robin?
你应该让她知道你的存在
You need to stay on her radar.
给她打电话
Call her right now.
她在飞机上 手机关机了
She's on the plane. Her phone's off.
哦 额滴神呀
Oh, my God!
当飞机着陆时 她打开手机
How adorable would it be if when the plane lands,
发现信箱里满是你的信息
she turns on her phone
超浪漫的哟
and her mailbox is full of messages from you?!
泰德 不要给她留语音信息
Ted, don't leave her any voice mails.
为什么不
Why not?
因为 因为你应该去俄罗斯
Because...Because you need to go to Russia.
带着满满的爱意
With love!
给她一个惊喜
Surprise her.
做些不煞风景
Make the--in no way creepy--
罗宾也超喜欢的浪漫行为
grand romantic gesture that we all know Robin loves.
哦
Oh!
所以我应该带她去红场散步
So I just walk up to her in Red Square
再带一束玫瑰
with a dozen roses?
或者乘着我的热气球
Or float down to her
降落在她的面前
in my hot air balloon
带着十束玫瑰
with ten dozen roses!
对 完美了
Yes, that's perfect!
不是这样的 莉莉
Not like this, Lily.
不是这样
Not like this.
我先回去下 我还要写一些十四行诗
If you'll excuse me, I've got some sonnets to write.
坐下 泰德 你会想听这个的
Stay put, Ted. You're gonna want to hear this.
伙计们 这是啥
Guys, what's this?
马修和莉莉开始解释了
And Marshall and Lily explained.
这是从十年前开始的
It all started ten years earlier.
他们在寻找一个爱好
They had been looking for a new hobby
作为夫妻可以一起分享的爱好
they could do as a couple.
我已经错过了新手课程
I already missed the beginner's lesson.
也许我不该去
Maybe I shouldn't even go.
啊 不管了
Ah, screw it.
我看过奥运会的 我知道怎么滑
I've seen the Olympics. I know what I'm doing.
我滑雪去喽 衰人们
I'm going skiing, bitches!
他必然会摔断腿
He's gonna break his leg.
他不会的
He's not gonna break his leg.
我赌20刀他会
20 bucks says he does.
莉莉和马修打赌
"Lily bets Marshall
说泰德会在滑雪时摔断腿
that Ted will break his leg skiing."
你们绝对不会相信的
You would be amazed.
从缆车上掉下来的人可多了
People fall off ski lifts all the time.
呃 上厕所去也
Well, I gotta hit the head.
好吧 断的不是腿
Well, he didn't break his leg.
其实 我想说的 呃
Yeah, I gotta say that, um,
打赌赢钱让我感觉
making money off this bet just makes me feel...
从没这么年轻过是吧
More alive than you've felt in years?
正解 新爱好
Yes! New hobby!
我们需要一个钱箱 一些亮片和胶水
We need a cash box, some glitter and some glue!
你们一直在拿我们打赌吗
You've been betting on us?
好像我们是一堆在某个
Like we're a couple of hobos
二逼高富帅的后院里
fighting over a sandwich
抢三明治的流浪汉
in some psycho preppy kid's backyard?
才不是 这不过是婚姻的产物
No, this is just what happens in marriage.
你会觉得无聊
You get bored.
找不到事情做
You run out of things to do.
我们都到做模型的地步了
We were making models.
你们这些老光棍在外面
You single people are out there
整天喝酒睡女人
with the drinking and the sleeping around...
飞机模型
Model airplanes.
郎情妾意 跨凤乘龙
The grinding and the bumping
玉体横陈 香汗淋漓
and the hot sweaty bodies.
还有会转的小螺旋桨
...with little propellers that spin.
诶 这个蛮有意思的
Oh, this one looks interesting.
莉莉 我以为你说你想要的
Lily, I thought you said you wanted to.
你的主意啊
It was your idea.
我节食一周就为了可以上镜
I starved myself for a week to get camera-ready.
你早餐时吃了个熊掌面包啊
You had a bear claw for breakfast.
对啊 就一个熊掌面包啊
Yeah, a bear claw.
我 我改主意了
I-I changed my mind.
我不想让巴尼看到我们那啥
I-I just don't want Barney to see us doing it.
巴尼永远不会发现的
Barney is never gonna see this.
算了吧 巴尼是大神啊
Oh, come on. It's Barney.
他终归会看到的
Eventually, somehow he's gonna see it.
想赌吗
Want to bet?
这么说 还真有黄带啊
So there really is a sex tape.
简单的说 这些长期赌局
Anyhoozles, just... long-term bets,
就是我们犯二的时候打的
just a silly thing we do.
你怎么样啊 泰德
What about you, Ted?
发型不错哟
Your hair's looking good.
莉莉和马修打赌说泰德和罗宾
"Lily bets Marshall that Ted and Robin
最后是不会在一起的
won't end up together."
好嘛
Wow.
这么一来就水落石出了
So now it's becoming clear why...
你们这样极尽可能的毁掉我未来的幸福
you've been trying to sabotage my future happiness.
就他妈为了赢一个赌
To win a bet.
算了吧 泰德
Come on, Ted.
这个赌我们已经打了很久了
We made that bet so long ago.
而且 兄弟啊 这个赌真是太让人抓狂了
And boy, it's been a real nail-biter.
泰德和斯黛拉都订婚了
Ted and Stella got engaged.
给钱
Pay up.
还没定论呢
Not yet.
我们正在驱车前往婚礼现场哦
We are driving to the wedding.
给钱
Pay up.
再等等
Not yet.
我们就在婚礼现场哟
We are at the wedding.
给钱
Pay up.
还没完
Not yet.
擦
Damn it.
我真是不敢相信
I can't believe you guys!
我被人丢在神坛
I got left at the alter,
而你们关心的就只是个破赌吗
and all you cared about was some stupid bet?
我一直都支持你 但我……
I never stopped rooting for you, but I...
泰德 我从来没有跟你唱过反调
Ted, I'm not rooting against you.
我就是觉得罗宾不适合做你妻子
I just don't think Robin's the girl you marry.
这就是我最初打这个破赌的原因
That's why I made the stupid bet to begin with.
我想说 没错 都过去五年了
I mean, yes, it's five years later,
你还没有找一个人安定下来
and you haven't settled down with anyone else,
但是你和罗宾也没有往这方面靠啊
but you haven't settled down with Robin, either.
这里面一定有原因的
There must be a reason for that.
到底哪里不对劲
What's standing in the way?
上帝啊
God...
如果你帮我找到黄带
if you help me find this sex tape,
我将洗心革面 重新做人
I am going to make some changes in my life.
我再也不沾花惹草
I am going to stop sleeping around,
再也不酗酒 不搞恶作剧
quit drinking so much, no more shenanigans.
我将全心全意 尽我所能
I am going to devote my entire life
行善布施 赞美汝名
to doing good deeds,and praising your name.
你要找的是这个吗 巴尼先森
Is this what you're looking for, Mr. Barney?
不用了 兄弟 找着了
Never mind, bro. Found it.
我找到了
I found it!
伟大的耶稣安拉毛主席啊 我找着了 泰德
Sweet glory hallelujah, I found it, Ted.
你是我认识的唯一一个还有录像机的二货
You're the only idiot I know who still owns a VCR,
所以恭喜 你赢得了唯一一张
so you are the lucky winner of the
和我一起围观我们最好的朋友们
"Who gets to sit next to me and watch our best friends
欲火焚身走火入魔”奖券
go bananas all over each other"" sweepstakes.
向老掉牙的视频神器致敬
To the outdated viewing device!
然后我终于明白了我和罗宾
And then I realized why Robin and I
五年了还没有复合的原因
hadn't gotten back together in the last five years.
噢 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
罗宾爱的人是你啊
Robin's in love with you.
我之前居然都没注意到
I can't believe I didn't see it before.
罗宾一直爱着你
Robin is in love with you.
不 相信我 她没有
No, she's not. Trust me.
不 她爱你
Yes, she is.
你们之间发生了什么
Something happened between you guys.
导致你和诺拉分手
That's why you broke up with Nora.
那天晚上 我见你在她房间里
That night, I saw you in her room,
房间里有玫瑰花瓣 蜡烛
there were rose petals, candles...
你看见了
You saw that?
那你估计还看到
Well, then, maybe you also saw
花瓣和蜡烛统统被丢进了垃圾袋里
those rose petals and candles going into a garbage bag.
接着巴尼告诉我发生的一切
And then Barney told me everything.
他和罗宾的一夜情
How he and Robin hooked up.
他为了罗宾和诺拉分手
How he broke up with Nora to be with her.
他想着罗宾也会为他做同样的事情
How he thought she would do the same for him.
罗宾是如何伤了他的心
How she broke his heart.
她选择了凯文
She chose Kevin.
我是非常伤心 但我想
It hurt, but...
他们是相爱的吧
I guess they're in love.
他们昨晚分手了
They broke up last night.
可惜
Bummer.
管他呢 咱先拿马修和莉莉的性爱录像带打些赌吧
Anyway, let's make our own bets about this sex tape.
我说马修身上肯定有一处穿孔
I've got Marshall with a surprise piercing
赔率5:1
at five-to-one odds,
莉莉修剪过"着陆区"赔率10:1
Lily with a landing strip, ten-to-one,
马修修剪过"着陆区"赔率1:1
Marshall with a landing strip, even money.
我才不信这鬼话
I don't believe this.
你爱过罗宾
You were in love with Robin,
现在你知道她分手了 你的反应就是"可惜"
you find out she's single, and your reaction is "Bummer"?
那你想让我说什么 泰德
What do you want me to say, Ted?
我以为我们之间有什么
Whatever I thought was there,
她却不这么想
she thought differently.
所以说...不 罗宾现在单身不关我什么事
So... no, I don't care that Robin is single again.
这样的话 如果罗宾跟别人恋爱 你不介意吗
So if Robin started dating someone else, you wouldn't mind?
不
Nope.
就算和她谈恋爱的那个人是我
Even if that somebody else was me?
就算和她谈恋爱的那个人是你
Even if that somebody else was you.
--真的吗 --真的
Really? Really.
嘿 哥们比娘们重要 对吧
Hey, bros before hos, right?
无论罗宾伤我多深
No matter how mad she made me,
她永远是我哥们
Robin's still my bro.
如果 呃 你能让她开心的话
And if, uh, you make her happy,
我也会开心
then that makes me happy.
巴尼 你知道吗 你真的长大成熟了
Barney, you've really grown up, you know that?
谢谢
Thanks.
现在来看咱们俩朋友的性爱录像带吧
Now let's watch our two best friends have sex on tape.
我去做爆米花
I'll make the popcorn.
别看那盘带子
Don't watch that tape!
要看那盘带子
Watch that tape!
诶呀 不好意思 我就是想赢得那个赌注
Well, sorry, I just really want to win the bet.
现在 放映开始
And here we go.
好好好 好吧 巴尼
O-okay. Okay, fine, Barney.
看我们有点淫荡的家庭录影吧 但你可先听好了
Watch our dirty little home movie, but be forewarned,
在一分钟那儿
at about the one minute mark,
你会看到我做这个表情
you're going to see me make this face.
天啊 那是咱骑摩托车时
Oh, God, that's the face you made
-你脸上的表情 -是啊
the day we rode motorcycles. Yeah.
是啊是啊 你真想看吗
Yeah. You really want to see that?
而且 你想听我发出这个声音吗
A-and do you want to hear me go, uh...
不可能是这个声音 不可能
It can't sound like that. It can't.
我认得那个声音 我隔着墙听到过
I know that noise, I've heard it through the walls.
我以为哪个邻居养了只病猫呢
I thought the neighbors had a sick cat.
好吧 巴尼 你可要知道
Okay, but, Barney, just remember,
你也会看到好多这个
you'll also be seeing a lot of this:
喔耶~~  喔~~ 耶~~
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
就像这样 但那时我没怀孕
It's this, but I'm not pregnant.
我皮肤跟大象的一样 松垮垮的
My skin is loose, like an elephant.
我的咪咪又大又活泼
My boobs are perky and plump.
我的呻吟犹如一条蔫不拉几的老狗
I slobber like a confused old dog.
-我打我自己的屁股  -我打我自己的屁股
I slap my own ass. I slap my own ass!
巴尼
Barney...
那是哥的录像机
that was my VCR.
泰德
Ted...
那不过是一台录像机
it was a VCR.
一周后 罗宾回来了 我去机场接了罗宾
A week later, I picked Robin up at the airport.
她给我讲了俄国之行的很多事情
She told me all about her trip.
接着我带她去她最爱的饭店吃饭
And took her out to dinner at her favorite restaurant.
夜晚将尽时 有一件事算是清楚了
And by the end of the night,one thing had become clear:
我们两个不会有结果 是吧
It's not going to happen, is it?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
是因为巴尼
It's because of Barney.
什么
What?
才不是
No.
巴尼和我  我们
Barney and I... we...
不  不  就是
No. No. It's just...
你知道 最近的事情太疯狂了
You know, things have just been so crazy lately.
我生命中的一切都那样  不稳定
Everything in my life is... unstable.
在为数不多的事物中 只有你是我可以依赖的
I mean, you're one of the few things that I can count on.
我真的不想把这一切都搞砸
And... I really don't want to mess that up.
我们...  我们还有那个约定 是吧
We-we... we still have our deal, right?
如果我们都...在40岁的时候还单身的话
If we're both still...single when we're 40?
是啊 是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
不 对不起 罗宾
No. Look... I'm sorry.
我 我不能守着那个约定了
I-I can't do that anymore.
只要那扇门还开着一点点
As long as the door is even a little bit open,
我就有这感觉 我就想着
I have this feeling that I'll just be...
等下去 等到你40岁 看我还能不能和你在一起
waiting around to see if I win the lottery when you turn 40.
我想你明白你现在对我的感觉
I think you know how you feel about me now,
我觉得 时间不会改变这一切
and... I don't think time's going to change that.
请告诉我
Just tell me.
你爱我吗
Do you love me?
不爱
No.
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们做朋友挺好的
We're great as friends.
让我们
Let's just...
忘了刚刚我说的话吧
Let's just forget I ever said anything.
酒吧 你自个 马上
Bar. Alone. Now.
这只是路上的一个小障碍而已
It's just a bump in the road.
你们注定要在一起的
You guys are meant to be together.
你可不能放弃啊
You can't give up.
你们还是有可能的啊
You... i-it can still happen.
没可能了 马修
No. Marshall...
要不你试试带着十束玫瑰
What about the hot air balloon thing,
乘热气球那招
with the ten dozen roses?
-还有你那首十四行诗写得咋样了 -老兄
-And how's the sonnet coming, buddy? -Dude.
你打赌押错对象了 别挣扎了
You bet on the wrong horse. Let it go.
不管你信不信
Believe it or not,
我对这事儿还有点开心
I'm happy about this. I'm...
我终于可以继续往前看了
I can finally move on.
这可是件好事
This is a good thing.
真的
Really.
嘿 罗宾
Hey, Robin.
- 嗨
-Oh, hey. - Hey.
嘿 我差点都忘了 这是莉莉的吹风机
Hey. Uh, look, before I forget,here's Lily's hairdryer.
我好像都借了几百年了
I borrowed it, like,a million years ago.
没事 你留着用吧
Yeah, you can keep that.
呃 是这样的
Um... Hey, listen,
泰德告诉我了你们的事儿
Ted told me what happened with you guys,
他还说 他能够平静的接受
and he says that he's at peace with it.
噢 是吗
Oh, really?
挺好的
That's good.
他说谎了 罗宾
He's lying, Robin.
他只是想表现得很坚强 但他还是很难受
He's trying to be strong,but it's killing him,
所以 作为他最好的朋友
and so, as his best friend,
我必须告诉你
I have to say something that...
他太爱你了 以至于说不出口
he loves you just way too much to say.
你得搬出去了
You gotta move out.
我知道
I know.
Shake It Out- Florence+The Machine
所有的食尸鬼都出来玩耍
? And all of the ghouls come out to play ?
所有的恶魔都想要他的鲜肉
? And every demon wants his pound of flesh ?
但是我更愿意独自保留些东西
? But I like to keep some things to myself ?
我更愿意保持坚强
? I like to keep my issues strong ?
黎明之前总是最黑暗的
? It's always darkest before the dawn ?
我曾是一个傻瓜 我也曾盲目
? And I've been a fool and I've been blind ?
我无法把过往抛在身后
? I can never leave the past behind ?
我看不到路
? I can see no way ?
我总是拖着马四处游荡
? I'm always dragging that horse around ?
有趣的是 从某种疯狂的角度来说 我有点开心
here's funny thing, In my own crazy way, I was kind of happy.
过了这么多年 这是我第一次
For the first time in years,there was no little part of me
对和罗宾在一起不再抱任何幻想
clinging to the dream of being with Robin.
这也意味着 这么多年来
Which meant, for the first time in years,
我的世界第一次变得如此宽广
the world was wide open.
因为 孩子们
Because, kids...
当一扇门关闭的时候
when a door closes,
下一句 你懂的
well...you know the rest
看在泰德的份上 我很不想提这事
- For Ted's sake,I hate to say this,
但是  给钱吧
but... pay up.
还没完呢
Not yet.